Hello hi
friends today I am going to share with you that
if you are
working as an agent in an insurance company and you want to
switch from one insurance company
to another insurance company then what will be the
process for that first of all
you will have to
cancel your agent code, to cancel you send
an email to the companies you are working for
and make sure that you have to
surrender your agent code, what does the company do,
so send an email to them automatically, if they do
not respond to it then
if you are not getting a response from this then
you should
put your mail ID in the list complaints and I don't gov.in in this, there will be only
one benefit of keeping this, then the
insurance company will
reply to you and as your license gets cancelled, you
can join your company and from there you
can do your business, if you have any
doubt then please
message me in the comment box, I will
check and reply to you  I will thank you very
much for watching my video